brandpointcontent.com 2019-04-09

# BrandpointContent - Privacy Policy

### Brandpoint Content Privacy Policy

BrandpointContent values you and your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, and use information provided by you through this website, with a home page located at www.brandpointcontent.com.

Note: This is a B-2-B (Business to Business) website.This website is not intended for general consumers. Although anyone may view the home page of this website and limited additional content, full access to this website is granted only to those who have registered their business, providing their name, business, and other information. If you are not a business publisher or advertiser, please do not attempt to create an account or to view any restricted content on this website.

Non-Personal Information and Cookies   
When you visit our Site we collect certain non-personal information from your computer. This information is collected from your computer’s web browser and may include information such as the following (“non-personal information”):

  * the type of web browser software you use (for example, Internet Explorer)
  * the name of the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, Yahoo.com)
  * the date and time you access our websites, as well as which pages were viewed

We will use non-personal information to help us make our websites more useful to visitors and for other business purposes. We may use information from cookies to deliver content that you may find more interesting based upon the articles you have viewed in the past. We may prepare reports and other materials using non-personal information. We may share and use non-personal information without restriction because it does not identify who you are.

What information does BrandpointContent require for registration?   
BrandpointContent asks that you provide:

  * Your Name
  * Your Title
  * Your Company
  * Your Company’s Address
  * Your Phone Number
  * Your E-mail Address
  * Additional contact and business information

All of the above information, which specifically identifies who you are, is considered "personal information". We use personal information to track who is using this site. We may use personal information for the following purposes: to contact you, to operate or improve our business, to share your information with our affiliate companies, vendors, or others who offer products / services in which you may be interested, to protect our rights, to comply with any law or legal request, to provide information to any successor entity to our business by way of merger, sale, transfer of assets, or similar transaction.

Links and Advertisers On This Site  
This website contains links to other websites, including to sites operated by advertisers that are clients of ARA. We provide these links for your convenience, but we do not review, control, or monitor the privacy practices of other sites. We are not responsible for the performance of these sites or for your business dealings with them. Your use of other web sites is subject to the terms and conditions of those sites, including the privacy policies of those sites. Please note that we may allow third party advertisers to place ads on our pages. Those ads may include cookies. Our advertisers» use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this Policy BrandpointContent also obtains a cookie at sign-up.

What is a cookie?  
A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your computer’s hard drive when you visit them. BrandpointContent will only use cookies to make your experience at our Web site more pleasant and never to track personally identifiable information about you. It is used for automatic login - so you don’t need to login each time you view an article. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites.

Can I eliminate my information from BrandpointContent’s database?  
Yes. BrandpointContent’s Opt-Out Policy is this: If at any time you would like to discontinue your relationship or part of your relationship with BrandpointContent, simply contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) to be removed.

Can I update my information with BrandpointContent?  
If at any time you believe the information submitted to or collected by BrandpointContent is in any way incorrect, simply update your information under the ’My Account’ link located on the upper right of the screen.

How do I indicate that I accept BrandpointContent’s Privacy Policy?  
By using our Web site (www.brandpointcontent.com) you indicate your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you disagree with all or any part of our Privacy Policy, you must stop using this site promptly; however you may first delete your account information.

Policy Changes  
This Policy was last updated on March 10, 2010. We will post any changes to the Privacy Policy to this page or a similar page on our website. Please return and check it regularly to be certain you are aware of this Policy at all times. We reserve the right to change this Policy at any time, and your continued use of this website constitutes your agreement to such changed Policy.

Data Processed in US  
By providing any information to us through this website, all users, including without limitation users in the member states of the European Union, fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection, storage, forward transfer, and processing of such information in the United States of America.

Data Security  
We take steps to protect personal information about you when we receive and store it. We have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information under our control. We limit and control the number of employees who have access to this website’s servers and databases. You agree, however, that no organization can promise perfect security, and that we are not responsible for the illegal acts of third parties.

Contact Us  
If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or send us a letter addressed by First Class Postage Prepaid U.S. Mail or overnight courier to the following address: 

Privacy Officer, ARANet, Inc.  
850 Fifth Street South,   
Hopkins, MN
